Okay, so if you're watching this video, it
means that we booked a call and you
are wondering what is actually included in
the contractor growth engine and what
we do for you and what you don't have to
worry about anymore.
So first things first is the things you
will never have to do again when working
with us, right? You never have to film an
ad, you have to write any ads, you
have to sit with tire kicker leads, you
don't have to chase any leads by hand,
and you don't have to guess which ads
actually paid for themselves and which ads
are actually contributing to the jobs,
right? Not just generating leads, right?
Our system puts everything together. We
target, we build the creative.
We run the ads. We set all of the
automatic follow-ups that go out to these
leads. We're calling these leads within
five minutes and we're booking them on
estimates, qualifying them, and everything
is automatically reported with our
internal software. So there's a couple of
different pillars to our specific
system. The first one is traffic.
We're optimizing for booked estimates, not
just getting their contact info.
We're not optimizing these ads just to get
the leads through the door.
We're optimizing them to actually book
real estimates and get jobs.
We're placing these ads in front of
homeowners who are actually wanting your
services, not 15 year old kids these are
people that actually need your service
and have high intent we build the
creatives from scratch and test them
creatives that are already proven in your
market so we do all the market
research we take all the ads that are
actually proven and we test our own
variations right the point of this is for
you to become a kingpin in your market
we want to conquer your local market right
so that is just traffic step two is
conversion so conversion is automatic
follow-ups that go out the second the lead
comes in and then nurture them through a
seven day window right we're also speed
to lead dialing we're calling all of these
leads within five minutes of them
coming in. Harvard actually did a study
where if you do not call a lead that
comes from cold outbound traffic within
five minutes the chance of them
converting goes down 99%, so we make sure
we're calling these leads right away
right and with all these follow-ups so
automatic follow-ups are going out but
these are personalized right they're not
generic automated messages that sound
like a robot these are personalized and
then to double back off that is whenever
we book an actual estimate whenever a lead
is qualified we're helping you close
by sending them pre nurturing assets right
So say your close rate is maybe a 20
or 25%, it could shoot up to a 35 40% just
off of, you know, these leads being
pre nurtured with the assets we're sending
them, right? So that is conversion.
That is step two, pillar two, right?
Pillar three is reporting.
So our internal custom software gives full
transparency to you about every
single ad, where every single lead is,
right?
We have different pipelines that we use
internally and we don't want you to see
all this mess, right? So we just have a
very simple graph and it shows you where
each lead is in the process. So yeah,
that's basically it for that.
But what happens once we actually book an
estimate?
Inside of the software, you literally
click two buttons.
If you, say you close, you put them on a
job, you literally click close and then
you book the job. It's as simple as that
and it reports everything.
You don't have to worry about going back
and forth with me.
You get your numbers real time.
So another big aspect, now this isn't a
pillar, this is just, you know, kind of
how everything works is over time, our
budget is moving towards the ads that are
actually producing. So over time, it's
compounding results, right?
Because leads are not hard to generate.
Anyone can go on Facebook ads and maybe
generate a lead if you're somewhat
competent, right? You can generate some
leads with pretty bad ads.
It's hard to get high quality ads or high
quality leads though, because, you
know, you have to target your ads and you
have to build them in specific ways
and you have to let the pixel, let the
data sets inside Facebook learn and
actually produce high quality leads.
So that's why over time we keep generating
results for you because we know which
ads work and we compound the results so
basically that is the whole entire
system in in a very you know basic manner
basically all you have to do is fill
out an onboarding form you know show up to
a couple calls show up to the
estimates close the jobs and tap two
buttons that's literally all you have to
the whole entire time you know we handle
everything else the market research ad
creatives ad targeting lead qualification
literally everything right we're doing
everything  but yeah so that is the system
i just want to give a quick rundown
so you just have more clarity on the
actual call.
But you know, I look forward to speaking
and you know, let's get it moving.